You have returned to the situation from before.
Where are you?
Where is the center of awareness?
No need to decide.
Just notice what you feel and what you see.
Stay in this state.
Now the body that you see will slowly disappear.
Where are you?
Where is the center of awareness?
Look at your hands.
Now the body that you see from will slowly disappear.
Where are you?
Where is the center of awareness?
Without a bodily anchor.
Where are you?
What is the center of awareness?
What is it good for?
Notice this state.
Hold this state.
Whatever appears, sounds, visions, feelings, let them come and go.
Now the body that you see from before will slowly disappear.
Just notice and stay in this state.